Council of National Organizations Records
Council of National Organizations Records
1951-1966
Council of National Organizations (U.S.)
14.0 linear ft.
The Council of National Organizations gathers information on educational agencies for public use. Collection includes general files containing correspondence and printed material on member groups.
148908
Biographical History
The Council of National Organizations for Adult Education (CNO) was founded in 1952 as a subsidiary organization of the American Education Association of the USA, or AEA-USA (now the American Association for Adult and Continuing Education or AAACE). "to establish closer communication and exchange of experience between organizations and individuals working in different fields." Its primary function was to gather information on educational agencies for public use.
Scope and Contents of the Collection
The Council of National Organizations Records contains a single series, General files. Most of the material ison specific councils, organizations, associations, U.S. government departments, etc., and the folders contain either correspondence or printed information.
Arrangement of the Collection
The files remain in the order they were received, and are in neither alphabetical nor chronological order.
Related Material
has the papers and records of numerous organizations and individuals relating to adult education. Please refer to for a complete listing. The interested researcher may also wish to refer to the Alexander Charters Library of Resources for Educators of Adults (http://scrc.syr.edu/charterslibrary).
Subject and Genre Headings
Adult education; Council of National Organizations (U.S.) -- Archives.; Council of National Organizations (U.S.) -- Records and correspondence.; Adult education -- United States.; Adult education -- Information services.; Adult education -- Societies, etc.; Education -- United States.; Education -- Information services.; Education -- Societies, etc.; Correspondence.; Minutes (administrative records); Newsletters.; Adult education.
Access Restrictions
The majority of our archival and manuscript collections are housed offsite and require advanced notice for retrieval. Researchers are encouraged to contact us in advance concerning the collection material they wish to access for their research.
Inventory
- General files
  - Clearing House Committee, 1952 (Box 1)
  - Education for Democracy, Committee on, 1952 (Box 1)
  - Nominating Committee, 1953-1955; 3 folders (Box 1)
  - Participants, Committee on, 1953 (Box 1)
  - Participating Organizations, Committee on, 1952 (Box 1)
  - Nominating Committee, 1952 (Box 2)
  - Local-National Communication on Adult Education (Box 2)
  - Executive Committee, 1953-1955; 3 folders (Box 2)
  - Planning Committee - General, 1952 (Box 2)
  - Financial Statements, 1954 (Box 2)
  - Budget, 1953 (Box 2)
  - Finance - Waldie, Aieleen (Box 2)
  - Fund for Adult Education, 1952; 1953 (Box 2)
  - Materials Evaluation (Box 2)
  - Television, 1955 (Box 2)
  - Television Committee, June 1953 and 1954 (Box 2)
  - Educational TV Work Session, Jan., 1953 (Box 2)
  - TV Conference, Sept. 7, 1954 (Box 2)
  - Educational TV Minutes and Reports, 1952; 1953 (Box 2)
  - TV Meeting - Chicago, Washington, New York (Box 2)
  - Hancock Foundation, Allan (Box 2)
  - Educational TV - Administration, 1953 (Box 2)
  - Educational TV - Promotion (Box 2)
  - National Information Bureau (Box 2)
  - National Association of Public School Educators (NAPSAE) (Box 2)
  - National Social Welfare Assembly (Box 2)
  - Students and Studies and Jobs to 1955 (Box 2)
  - Test Cities (Box 2)
  - Newsletter Committee, 1952 (Box 2)
  - Materials Packets - Evaluations and Comments Program Guide, 1954 (Box 2)
  - Program Guide, 1955-1956 (Box 2)
  - Sales TV - A New Community Resource (Box 2)
  - Invitations, 1954 (Box 2)
  - Invitations to Participate, 1953 (Box 2)
  - Council Meeting, 1957 (Box 2)
  - Committees, discontinued (Box 2)
  - Finance Committee, 1955; 1959 (Box 3)
  - Finance Committee (Box 3)
  - Finance Interpretation Meetings, invitations, responses (Box 3)
  - Financial Statements, 1955-1957; 2 folders (Box 3)
  - Proposed New Letterhead, Feb., 1962 (Box 3)
  - Fund For Adult Education, 1953-1957 (Box 3)
  - Fund for Adult Education proposals (Box 3)
  - Annual Meeting (Box 3)
  - Council Meeting Arrangements, 1956 (Box 3)
  - Council Meeting - Master File, 1955 (Box 3)
  - Annual Meeting - Work Groups, 1955 (Box 3)
  - Work Groups, 1954 (Box 3)
  - 1954 Meeting - Master File Material (Box 3)
  - 1954 Council Meeting Committee Planning (Box 3)
  - 1953 Conference - Master File of Material (Box 3)
  - Conference Work Groups, 1953 (Box 3)
  - Conference - Master File of Material, 1952 (Box 3)
  - Conference - Work Groups, 1952 (Box 3)
  - Dr. Lindeman's Speech, Council Meeting, 1952 (Box 3)
  - National Council for Community Improvement (Box 3)
  - NAM Educational Advisory Council (Box 3)
  - National Project in Agricultural Communications (Box 3)
  - Organizations, Council of National Organizations of Adult Education Association of the U.S. (Box 3)
  - New York University Cooperation (Box 3)
  - Nominating, 1961 (Box 3)
  - Nominating, Robert Allen, 1961 (Box 3)
  - Nominating Committee, 1960 (Box 3)
  - Annual Meeting, 1964 (Box 4)
  - Adult Education Association (Box 4)
  - Correspondence "A" (Box 4)
  - Correspondence "B" (Box 4)
  - Budgets, 1964-1965 (Box 4)
  - Untitled Folder (Box 4)
  - Correspondence "C" (Box 4)
  - Correspondence "D" (Box 4)
  - Correspondence "E" (Box 4)
  - Executive Committee Meetings (Box 4)
  - Correspondence "F" (Box 5)
  - Correspondence "G" (Box 5)
  - Correspondence "H" (Box 5)
  - Correspondence "I" and "J" (Box 5)
  - Correspondence "K" and "L" (Box 5)
  - Correspondence "M" and "N" (Box 5)
  - Member Organizations, 1964-1965 (Box 5)
  - Miscellaneous Conferences, 1964-1965 (Box 5)
  - Correspondence "O", "P", and "Q" (Box 5)
  - Publications, 1964-1965 (Box 5)
  - Correspondence "R" (Box 5)
  - Correspondence "S" (Box 5)
  - Correspondence "T" (Box 5)
  - Correspondence "U", "V", and "W" (Box 5)
  - Correspondence "X", "Y", and "Z" (Box 5)
  - Probing Volunteer-Staff Relations (Box 5)
  - Voluntary Giving for Community Health and Welfare Services (Box 5)
  - Miscellaneous papers (Box 5)
  - Leaflets
    - Eternal light
    - Council of National Organizations for Adult Education (Box 5)
    - Office of Community Advisory Services (Box 5)
    - Council of National Organizations for Adult Education (Box 5)
    - Citizens Committees...for Better Schools (Box 5)
    - Services for Families Living in Public Housing Advertisement (Box 5)
  - Council Meeting - Special, June 22, 1959 (Box 6)
  - Council Meeting, Arrangements, 1959 (Box 6)
  - Council Meeting Planning Committee, 1960 (Box 6)
  - Council Meeting, 1958 (Box 6)
  - Delegate Assembly Slate, 1961 (Box 6)
  - Delegate Assembly, DALarge, 1960 (Box 6)
  - Delegate Assembly Slate, 1959 (Box 6)
  - Delegates-at-Large, D.A., 1959 (Box 6)
  - Development Plan, Questionnaire Re: (Box 6)
  - Development Plan (Box 6)
  - Education - Ad Hoc (Box 6)
  - Education - Community Relations Institute, 1955 (Box 6)
  - First National City Bank through 1957 (Box 6)
  - Inter Association, 1958-1959 (Box 6)
  - Inter Association Conference, 1956-1957 (Box 6)
  - Inter Association, Chicago (Box 6)
  - Inter Association, Atlantic City, 1955 (Box 6)
  - International Project Committee (Box 6)
  - International Project, 1957-1960 (Box 6)
  - Israel Adult Education Seminar (Box 6)
  - Kaplan, Abbott (Box 6)
  - Leadership Development, 1959 (Box 6)
  - Leadership of National Organizations on the U.S. Scene, 1960 (Box 6)
  - Liberal Curriculum Project Paid Bills (Box 6)
  - Liberal Curriculum - Publishers (Box 6)
  - Liberal Curriculum to Sept. 1959 (Box 6)
  - Leadership Development, 1957-1958 (Box 6)
  - Leadership Seminar, 1958 (Box 6)
  - Broadcasting Committee, radio, TV project (Box 7)
  - Broadcasting Committee, radio to Sept., 1959 (Box 7)
  - Broadcasting Committee, 1957-1958 (Box 7)
  - Budgets, 1952-1957; 2 folders (Box 7)
  - Business Industry Conference, May 25, 1959 (Box 7)
  - Business Industry Conference, Oct. 6-7, 1958 (Box 7)
  - Business Education Conference, Dec. 11, 1957 (Box 7)
  - Business Education Conference, June 1958 (Box 7)
  - Chicago - City Meetings, 1956-1960 (Box 7)
  - New York - City Meetings, 1956 (Box 7)
  - Washington - City Meetings, 1956 (Box 7)
  - Meetings - New York City, 1954-1955 (Box 7)
  - AEA Conference, 1961 (Box 7)
  - AEA Conference, 1960 (Box 7)
  - Conference Group of U.S. National Organizations on the United Nations (Box 7)
  - Consultants' Panel (Box 7)
  - Controversial Issues, 1955; 1956 (Box 7)
  - Controversial Issues Workshop, Oct. 1956 (Box 7)
  - Controversial Issues, 1957; 1958 (Box 7)
  - Controversial Subjects, Techniques on Handling, 1954 (Box 7)
  - Council Meeting, Arrangements, 1961 (Box 7)
  - Council Meeting, Program, 1961 (Box 7)
  - Council Meeting Committee, 1961 (Box 7)
  - Council Meeting, L. Hein's Original Report, 1961 (Box 7)
  - Council Meeting Program, 1960 (Box 7)
  - Council Meeting Arrangements, 1960 (Box 7)
  - Council Meeting, 1959 (Box 7)
  - Proceedings: Council of National Organizations of the Adult Education Association of the United States, 1 volume (Box 7)
  - Council Meeting, Program, 1959 (Box 7)
  - Council Of Chief State School Officers (Box 8)
  - Evangelical United Brethren Church (Box 8)
  - Federal Mediation and Conciliation Service (Box 8)
  - Federal Union, Inc. (Box 8)
  - Film Council of America (Box 8)
  - Friends Council on Education (Box 8)
  - General Federation of Women's' Clubs Girls' Clubs of America, Inc. (Box 8)
  - Girls Friendly Society of the U.S.A. Great Books Foundation (Box 8)
  - Household Finance Corporation (Box 8)
  - Industrial Audio Visual Association (Box 8)
  - Industrial Relations Counselors, Inc. (Box 8)
  - Institute of International Education (Box 8)
  - Joint Council on Educational Television (Box 8)
  - W.K. Kellogg Foundation (Box 8)
  - Lions International (Box 8)
  - League of Women Voters (Box 8)
  - National Art Education Association of the NEA (Box 8)
  - National Association and Council of Business Schools (Box 8)
  - National Association of County Agricultural Agents (Box 8)
  - National Association of Educational Broadcasters (Box 8)
  - National Association of Public School Adult Educators (NAPSAE) (Box 8)
  - National Association of Social Workers (Box 8)
  - National Audubon Society (Box 8)
  - National Catholic Rural Life Conference (Box 8)
  - National Civil Service League (Box 8)
  - National CIO Community Services Committee (Box 8)
  - National Congress of Colored Parents and Teachers (Box 8)
  - National Congress of Parents and Teachers (Box 8)
  - National Council of Catholic Women (Box 8)
  - National Council of Naturalization and Citizenship (Box 8)
  - National Education Association, Division of Lay Relationships (Box 8)
  - National Farmers Union (Box 8)
  - National Federation of Business and Professional Women's Clubs (Box 8)
  - National Federation of Music Clubs (Box 8)
  - National Federation of Settlements and Neighborhood Centers (Box 8)
  - National Grange, The (Box 8)
  - National Kindergarten Association (Box 8)
  - National League of Nursing Education (Box 8)
  - National Municipal League (Box 8)
  - National Planning Association (Box 8)
  - National Publicity Council for Health and Welfare (Box 8)
  - National Safety Council (Box 8)
  - National School Boards Association (Box 8)
  - National Society for Crippled Children and Adults (Box 8)
  - National Thrift Committee (Box 8)
  - National Urban League (Box 8)
  - National Vocational Agricultural Teachers Association, Inc. (Box 8)
  - National Women's' Forum, Inc. (Box 8)
  - Office of Civil Defense Mobilization (Box 8)
  - Newsweek Club Bureau (Box 8)
  - Presbyterian Board of Christian Education (Box 8)
  - Presbyterian Institute of Industrial Relations (Box 8)
  - Protestant Episcopal Church, Department of Christian Education (Box 8)
  - Public Affairs Committee (Box 8)
  - Public Relations Society of America (Box 8)
  - Race Relations Department, Congregational Christian Churches (Box 8)
  - Religious Education Association (Box 8)
  - Science Service (Box 8)
  - Seventh Day Adventists (Box 8)
  - Special Libraries Association (Box 8)
  - Speech Association of America (Box 8)
  - Tennessee Valley Authority (Box 8)
  - Training Within Industry Foundation (Box 8)
  - Twentieth Century Fund (Box 8)
  - United Automobile Workers, CIO (Box 8)
  - U.S. Civil Service Commission (Box 8)
  - U.S. Department of Agriculture, Bureau of Human Nutrition and Home Economics (Box 8)
  - Bureau of Prisons, Dept. of Justice (Box 8)
  - U.S. Dept. of Defense
    - Department of the Air Force (Box 8)
    - Coast Guard (Box 8)
    - U.S. Marine Corps (Box 8)
    - Department of the Navy (Box 8)
    - Office of Armed Forces Information and Education (Box 8)
  - U.S. Office of Education, F.S.A., Home Economics Education Service (Box 8)
  - U.S. Department of Health, Education, and Welfare, Public Health Service (Box 8)
  - U.S. Department of Labor, Women's Bureau (Box 8)
  - U.S. Department of the Interior, Bureau of Indian Affairs (Box 8)
  - U.S. Department of State (Box 8)
  - Veterans Administration (Box 8)
  - World Goodwill (Box 8)
  - CNO News, Pre-1960, 1 envelope (Box 8)
  - AEA Membership Campaign, National Organizations, 1958; 1959 (Box 8)
  - American Assembly (Box 8)
  - Balance Sheets, 1958-1960 (Box 8)
  - Broadcasting Committee, 1959 (Box 8)
  - Broadcasting Committee - Television (Box 8)
  - ABC Radio, Sept., 1959 (Box 8)
  - Project "Task Force" (Box 9)
  - California Task Force (Box 9)
  - "Project Task Force" (Box 9)
  - FAE News Digest (Box 9)
  - Founding Documents (Box 9)
  - American Academy of Political and Social Science (Box 9)
  - American Alumni Council (Box 9)
  - Hayes Beall (Box 9)
  - World Affairs Survey (Box 9)
  - American Association of Group Workers (Box 9)
  - American Association for Health, Physical Education, and Recreation (Box 9)
  - American Association for the Advancement of Science (Box 9)
  - American Association of Junior Colleges (Box 9)
  - American Association of Land-Grant Colleges and State Universities (Box 9)
  - American Association of Museums (Box 9)
  - American Association of Psychiatric Social Workers, Inc. (Box 9)
  - American Association of School Administrators (Box 9)
  - American Automobile Association (Box 9)
  - American Bar Association (Box 9)
  - American Council for the Community (Box 9)
  - American Council on Education (Box 9)
  - American Craftsmen's Education Council (Box 9)
  - American Dental Association (Box 9)
  - American Diabetes Association, Inc. (Box 9)
  - American Dietetic Association (Box 9)
  - American Education Fellowship (Box 9)
  - American Farm Bureau Federation (Box 9)
  - American Federation of the Arts (Box 9)
  - American Federation of Labor / Congress of Industrial Organizations (Box 9)
  - American Federation of State, County, and Municipal Employees (Box 9)
  - American Federation of Teachers (Box 9)
  - American Jewish Congress (Box 9)
  - American Labor Education Service (Box 9)
  - American Medical Association (Box 9)
  - American Planning and Civic Association (Box 9)
  - American Physical Therapy Association (Box 9)
  - American Political Science Association (Box 9)
  - American Psychiatric Association (Box 9)
  - American Psychological Association (Box 9)
  - American Public Health Association, Inc. (Box 9)
  - American Savings and Loan Institute (Box 9)
  - American Society of Training Directors (Box 9)
  - American Veterans Committee (Box 9)
  - American Vocational Association, Inc. (Box 9)
  - Association for Study of Community Organization (Box 9)
  - Association for Education by Radio, Television (Box 9)
  - Association of American Colleges (Box 9)
  - Association of American Evening Colleges (Box 9)
  - Big Brothers of America (Box 9)
  - Boy Scouts of America (Box 9)
  - Carnegie Corporation of 4eW York (Box 9)
  - Catholic Association for International Peace (Box 9)
  - Child Study Association of America (Box 9)
  - Church of the Brethren, Christian Education Commission, General Brotherhood Board (Box 9)
  - Committee for Economic Development (Box 9)
  - Confraternity of Christian Doctrine (Box 9)
  - Congregational Christian Churches, Division of Christian Education (Box 9)
  - Cooper Union for the Advancement of Science and Art (Box 9)
  - Correctional Education Association (Box 9)
  - 1954 Conference
    - Minutes (Box 10)
    - Lists (Box 10)
    - Memos (Box 10)
    - Committees (Box 10)
    - Program Guide (Box 10)
    - Projected Plans, 1954-1956 (Box 10)
  - Correspondence, 1953-1954 (Box 10)
  - Budget Summary, Feb. 1, 1953 to Dec. 31, 1954 (Box 10)
  - Undated Materials (Box 10)
  - Finance Committee, 1960 (Box 10)
  - Television Committee, 1952-1954 (Box 10)
  - Conference, Dec. 5-6, 1952 (Box 10)
  - Organizations Interested in CNO (Box 10)
  - Some CNO Minutes, 1951-1954 (Box 10)
  - CNO Correspondence, 1951-1952 (Box 10)
  - AEA Core Organizational Services, April 1954 (Box 10)
  - C - General, 1951-1954 (Box 10)
  - B - General, 1951-1954 (Box 10)
  - American Library Association, 1951-1954 (Box 10)
  - CNO Conference, 1953 (Box 10)
  - Miscellaneous Material (Box 10)
  - Council of National Organizations for Adult Education, 2 volumes (Box 10)
  - Executive Committee Meeting, Monday, Oct. 5, 1964 (Box 10)
  - Membership (correspondence), 1964 (Box 10)
  - Merrifield Book (Box 10)
  - Official Organizations Representatives to CNO (Box 10)
  - Volunteer Staff Relations Kit (Box 10)
  - Council of National Organizations for Adult Education (one volume) (Box 10)
  - Annual Meeting of the CNO, 1963 (Box 10)
  - CNO Annual Conference, Oct. 13-14, 1962 (Box 10)
  - CNO, 1964 (Box 10)
  - AEA (Box 10)
  - John Herring (CNO) (Box 10)
  - Treasurer (Keller) Correspondence (Box 10)
  - Annual Meeting, Dec. 7-9, 1964 (Box 10)
  - Annual Meeting, Reports and Minutes, 1964 (Box 10)
  - Annual Business Meeting, Dec. 8, 1964 (Box 10)
  - Annual Meeting Invitation Replies, 1964 (Box 10)
  - General Outline for Annual Meeting, Dec. 7-8, 1964 (Box 10)
  - Annual Conference Planning Committee, 1964 (Box 10)
  - Executive Committee Correspondence (Box 10)
  - Executive Committee, March 9, 1964 (Box 10)
  - Executive Committee, May 11, 1964 (Box 10)
  - Executive Committee Meeting, Sept. 14, 1964 (Box 10)
  - Workshop on Programmed Instruction, April 30, 1963 (Box 11)
  - Financial Statement and Dues Paid by Members, 1963 (Box 11)
  - "An Organization Self-Inventory" by Dorothy Parr (Box 11)
  - Pre-Publication Offer (Box 11)
  - Annual Meeting Announcement, 1963 (Box 11)
  - Nominating Committee Report and Elections, 1963 (Box 11)
  - Annual Meeting Program, Dec. 12-13, 1963 (Box 11)
  - Executive Meeting, Washington, D.C., 1963 (Box 11)
  - A Tool for Probing Volunteer-Staff Relations: An Organization Self-Inventory, 1963 (Box 11)
  - Change of Address Forms, 1963 (Box 11)
  - Leaflets (Box 11)
  - List of Members, 1963 (Box 11)
  - Preliminary Workshop Announcement, CNO Workshop, April, 30, 1963 (Box 11)
  - Copy from Committee Chairman for October CNO Newsletter, 1963 (Box 11)
  - CNO Membership Committee, 1962-1963 (Box 11)
  - CNO News, 1963 (Box 11)
  - Nominating Committee, 1963 (Box 11)
  - Project Committee, 1963 (Box 11)
  - Booklet Requests, 1963 (Box 11)
  - Mailing Lists, 1963 (Box 11)
  - Requests, 1962-1963 (Box 11)
  - Stationery, 1963 (Box 11)
  - Proposals Relating t o purposes and Structure to AEA - USA, 1963 (Box 11)
  - AEA Membership and Subscript ion Forms (Box 11)
  - Leadership in Voluntary Enterprise (Box 11)
  - Volunteer - Staff Relations Committee, 1963 (Box 11)
  - Correspondence, 1963 (Box 11)
  - Memo to: Executive Committee Members (Box 11)
  - Executive Committee, 1963 (Box 11)
  - Kit (Box 11)
  - Materials Exchange Service Correspondence (Box 11)
  - Materials Exchange Service, 1963 (Box 11)
  - Annual Meeting - Convention Bids (Box 11)
  - Annual Meeting, 1964 (Box 11)
  - Annual Meeting, 1963 (Box 11)
  - Agenda for CNO Executive Committee Meeting, 1963 (Box 11)
  - Membership, 1963 (Box 11)
  - BEC President, 1962-1963 (Box 11)
  - Petty Cash Statements, 1962-1963 (Box 11)
  - Re-organization (Box 11)
  - Planning Committee (Box 11)
  - Council of National Organizations - Conference in Washington, D.C., Nov., 1961 (Box 11)
  - Correspondence with CNO membership, 1966 (Box 11)
  - Council of National Organizations (Box 11)
  - Correspondence, Member Participation, 1958-1962 (Box 11)
  - Miscellaneous Material (Box 11)
  - Miscellaneous Material (Box 12)
  - An Alphabetical Listing, A-Z (Box 12)
  - Participation Committee through 1958 (Box 12)
  - Participation Rejected, 1954-1959 (Box 12)
  - Participation - Business Affiliates - Miscellaneous (Box 12)
  - Miscellaneous Material (Box 13)
  - Non-current CNO Committees, A-H (Box 13)
  - CNO Notebook (Box 13)
  - Executive Committee, Notebook, Dec. 1954-1959 (Box 13)
  - Non-Current CNO Committees, P-Z Notebook (Box 13)
  - Executive Committee, Meetings Material, Notebook, 1957-1959 (Box 13)
  - CNO Executive Committee, Notebook, 1951-1954 (Box 13)
  - Progress Reports, Annual Meeting Reports, Notebook (Box 13)
  - Non-Current CNO Committees, I-0 Notebook (Box 13)
  - OP Process Budgets, Partial Lists, Notebooks (Box 13)
  - Council of National Organizations, 1955 (Box 13)
  - Directory (Box 13)
  - Exchange Packet, 1955 (Box 13)
  - Executive Committee Minutes, 1955 (Box 13)
  - CNO News, 1955 (Box 13)
  - CNO Work Plan, June through December, 1955 (Box 13)
  - Other Reports, 1955 (Box 13)
  - Participant s (Box 13)
  - Proposal of Need (Box 13)
  - Television, 1955 (Box 13)
  - News, 1956-1958 (Box 13)
  - Council Broadcasting Committee (Box 13)
  - Directory (Box 13)
  - Conference, 1956 (Box 13)
  - Exchange Packet, 1956 (Box 13)
  - Council of National Organizations, 1956 (Box 13)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 13)
  - Executive Committee Minutes, 1956 (Box 13)
  - Inter-Association Conference (Box 13)
  - Participants (Box 13)
  - 1955-1956 Program Guide (Box 13)
  - Seminar (Box 13)
  - Projected Plans, 1954-1956 (Box 13)
  - Correspondence - General, Delegates-at-Large, E.S. (Box 14)
  - Correspondence to Executive Committees, to Membership (Box 14)
  - One unlabeled folder (Box 14)
  - Correspondence (Box 14)
  - News Correspondence re: E.S. (Box 14)
  - To Answer, E.S. (Box 14)
  - Correspondence - Treasurer (Keller), Expense Accounts, E.S. (Box 14)
  - One Unlabeled folder (Box 14)
  - Executive Committee and Special Meetings (Box 14)
  - Packet Survey, 1962 (Box 14)
  - Lists: Executive Committee, Participant Members, Correspondence re: Memberships (Box 14)
  - Minutes - Board of Trustee's Meeting, Nov. 1961; Jan. 1962 (Box 14)
  - Constitution, By-Laws, Jan. 1962; Revision Oct. 1962 (Box 14)
  - Ed Keller - Treasurer (Box 14)
  - Materials Exchange (Box 14)
  - three unlabeled folders (Box 14)
  - Experiment in Liberal Curriculum Development for National Organization Leadership (Box 14)
  - Creative leadership in Voluntary Enterprise (Box 14)
  - Leadership Development through Community Education (Box 14)
  - Leading Group Discussion, 2 volumes (Box 14)
  - CNO (Box 14)
  - One unlabeled folder (Box 14)
  - CNO (Box 14)
  - Minutes - Executive Committee Meetings (Box 14)
  - Unlabeled folder (Box 14)
  - News (Box 14)
  - Constitution and By-Laws (Box 15)
  - President's Letter (Box 15)
  - Service Fees, 1962 (Box 15)
  - Fund for Adult Education, 1958 (Box 15)
  - Unfiled Miscellaneous Data, Correspondence, 1964-1965 (Box 15)
  - Treasurer's... (Box 15)
  - Leadership in Voluntary Enterprise - Promotion (Box 15)
  - Liberal Curriculum Steering Committee (Box 15)